{
    "subject": "Eleanor_of_Alburquerque",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ferdinand_I_of_Aragon",
    "human_readable": "Eleanor of Alburquerque is married to Ferdinand I of Aragon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886869192123413,
            "question": "Is Ferdinand I of Aragon married to Eleanor of Alburquerque?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9593321084976196,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Eleanor of Alburquerque and Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9376327395439148,
            "question": "Who is Eleanor of Alburquerque married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.927338719367981,
            "question": "Who is Ferdinand I of Aragon married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9164933562278748,
            "question": "Eleanor of Alburquerque and Ferdinand I of Aragon were in a marital relationship. True or False?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819921612739563,
            "question": "To whom was Eleanor of Alburquerque wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8677471280097961,
            "question": "Can you name the wife of Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.79742830991745,
            "question": "What is the name of Ferdinand I of Aragon's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7960005402565002,
            "question": "What is the name of Eleanor of Alburquerque's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6358038783073425,
            "question": "Who was the queen of Ferdinand I of Aragon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eleanor of Alburquerque is married to Ferdinand I of Aragon.",
            "html": "yago_30278_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Eleanor of Alburquerque's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30278_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Ferdinand I of Aragon's wife?",
            "html": "yago_30278_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name the wife of Ferdinand I of Aragon?",
            "html": "yago_30278_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30278_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples for me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that Eleanor of Alburquerque was indeed married to Ferdinand I of Aragon, and they had several children together. This information can be found in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_30278/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt, which states that \"In 1394, Eleanor and Ferdinand were married.\" and lists their children."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Eleanor of Alburquerque (1374 \u2013 16 December 1435) was a Castilian noblewoman, Countess of Alburquerque, who became Queen of Aragon by her marriage to Ferdinand I of Aragon.\" and that she had children with him, indicating their marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}